In accordance with Article 13(1) and (2) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27

April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of

such data and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation, hereinafter: GDPR), we inform you that:

1. The administrator of your personal data is StrefaPi sp. z o.o. with its seat in Piaseczno 05-502, 10 Kmicica Street.

2. You can contact the Data Protection Officer on matters relating to data protection by writing to the email address

biuro@studiostawki.com or the address of the registered office.

3. Your personal data will be processed for the purpose of handling bookings and carrying out profiling, on the basis of

Article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR.

4. The recipients of your personal data will be the following entities: StrefaPi sp. z o.o.

5. Your personal data will be stored for a period of 10 years.

6. You have the right:

a. access to their personal data,

b. rectify your personal data,

c. delete your personal data,

d. restrict the processing of your personal data,

e. withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data by sending an e-mail to

biuro@studiostawki.com - if you have previously given your consent and the processing of data concerning

you is based on this consent,

f. portability of your personal data,

g. object to the processing of your personal data on grounds relating to your particular situation, in accordance

with Article 21 of the GDPR.

7. Notwithstanding the above, you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, i.e. the President of

the Office for Personal Data Protection (ul. Stawki 2, 00-193 Warsaw), if you consider that the processing of your

personal data violates the provisions of the GDPR.

8. Providing your personal data is a condition for concluding a contract. If you do not provide us with your personal

data, it will not be possible to book a studio - to provide a photographic service.

9. Your personal data will not be transferred outside the European Economic Area/to an international organisation.

10. Your data will be processed by automated means, including profiling. The consequence of profiling will be that a

profile will be assigned to a person in order to make decisions concerning him/her or to analyse or predict his/her

preferences, behaviour and attitudes.

StrefaPi sp. z o.o.

ul. Kmicica 10, 05-502 Piaseczno

NIP: 1231255781, KRS: 0000391945, REGON: 143191130
